Finding Aid for Margaret Bayne Price Papers 1918-1969
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
Oct. 5, 1949
Daley, Richard J., 1902-1976.
Aug. 3, 1956
Dempsey, John N. 1915-
Apr. 2, 1962
Diggs, Charles C.
Dec. 29, 1949, Nov. 16, 1956, Feb. 8, 1966
Dillon, C. Douglas, (Clarence Douglas), 1909-
Mar. 4, 1964
DiSalle, Michael V. (Michael Vincent), 1908-
May 2, 1956, Mar. 21, 1962
Douglas, Paul Howard, 1892-
Aug. 7, 1952, Sept. 21, 1952, 1963 undated, Mar. 29, 1966
Doyle, William F.
1949, 1951, Sept. 9, 1952, 1953, Apr. 6, 1954, July 12, 1955
Duke, Angier Biddle, 1915-
Jan. 11, 1963
Dunnigan, James P.
Oct. 31, 1949, Feb. 10, 1950, Mar. 1, 1954, 1955-1956
Edwards, India.
Aug. 6, 1948, Mar. 6, 1950, Apr. 10, 1950, May 1950, June 1, 1952, Aug. 27, 1952, May 22, 1953, July 29, 1953, June 27, 1962, 1964-1965
Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.
Nov. 28, 1955
Farley, James Aloysius, 1888-
May 2, 1962
Farrell, Lawrence Llewellyn, 1903-1971.
Oct. 1948, Dec. 12, 1948, 1949, Oct. 6, 1950, Jan. 12, 1951, Sept. 18, 1951, 1952, Sept. 16, 1953, Nov. 11, 1953, 1954, July 15, 1955, July 21, 1955, Oct. 28, 1955
Faubus, Orval Eugene, 1910-
Apr. 18, 1962
Ferency, Zolton A. 1922-
Oct. 21, 1963, May 5, 1964, Aug. 17, 1964, Mar. 2, 1965, Apr. 21, 1967
Fowler, Henry H., 1908-
Jan. 10, 1965, Jan. 15, 1965, Feb. 4, 1965
Freeman, Orville L.
July 20, 1955, Mar. 11, 1964
Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1908-
Feb. 19, 1958
Gore, Albert Arnold, 1907-
Sept. 20, 1954, Dec. 13, 1954
Griffiths, Hicks G., 1910-
Nov. 5, 1948, Dec. 12, 1948, Oct. 10, 1949, Nov. 1, 1949, Dec. 27, 1949, Feb. 28, 1950
Griffiths, Martha Wright, 1912-
Aug. 6, 1948, June 12, 1962, Mar. 31, 1966
Gronouski, John Austin, 1919-
Feb. 28, 1964, Mar. 4, 1964
Gruening, Ernest, 1887-1974
Aug. 23, 1965
Hannah, John A., 1902-
Sept. 6, 1950
Harriman, W. Averell, (William Averell), 1891-1986.
1952, Apr. 10, 1953, Feb. 22, 1956, Aug. 13, 1956
Harris, Fred R., 1930-
May 26, 1965
Hart, Adelaide, 1900-
Sept. 30, 1952, 1953-1954, Mar. 13, 1956, Aug. 6, 1956, Oct. 9, 1956, Jan. 22, 1958, 1959, 1963-1965, Apr. 25, 1967
Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.
Aug. 27, 1953, Nov. 2, 1955, Jan. 7, 1959, Feb. 10, 1960, Feb. 11, 1964, July 20, 1967
Hartke, Vance.
Aug. 21, 1961, Oct. 24, 1961
Hayden, Carl Trumbull, 1877-1972.
Mar. 9, 1964, Mar. 16, 1964
Hill, Lister, 1894-
Apr. 25, 1961
Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1905-
Apr. 29, 1955
Hodges, Luther Hartwell, 1898-1974.
Mar. 19, 1961, June 30, 1964
Holland, Spessard L. (Spessard Lindsey), 1892-1971.
Apr. 12, 1962
Hughes, Richard J., 1909-
Apr. 3, 1962, July 3, 1963, Jan. 28, 1966
Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978.
Sept. 26, 1952, Sept. 30, 1952, July 21, 1955, July 31, 1956, Nov. 16, 1956, Dec. 29, 1959, 1962, Mar. 29, 1965, 1966, Jan. 22, 1967
Brown, Muriel Buck Humphrey.
Nov. 17, 1964, Jan. 11, 1966, Feb. 8, 1966
Jackson, Henry M. (Henry Martin), 1912-1983.
Aug. 22, 1960, May 2, 1962, May 4, 1962
Jeffrey, Mildred, 1911-
Aug. 2, 1954, Nov. 15, 1954, July 6, 1956, July 17, 1956, Mar. 15, 1958, 1959, Feb. 11, 1960, Aug. 12, 1964, July 15, 1965, Aug. 27, 1965, July 20, 1967, Oct. 26, 1967
Jenkins, Walter.
Mar. 20, 1964
Johnson, Lady Bird, 1912-
Mar. 15, 1962, June 8, 1962, 1964-1965, Dec. 16, 1966, Jan. 27, 1967, Nov. 6, 1967
Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973.
July 28, 1956, Mar. 14, 1961, Sept. 13, 1961, June 8, 1962, June 13, 1962, 1964, Apr. 1965, Oct. 5, 1965, June 29, 1966, Oct. 13, 1966, Jan. 21, 1967, Oct. 26, 1967
Katzenbach, Nicholas deB. (Nicholas deBelleville), 1922-
Apr. 1, 1964
Kefauver, Estes, 1903-1963.
1952, 1955, June 28, 1956, Aug. 7, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956
Kefauver, Nancy Patterson.
Feb. 6, 1952, Aug. 25, 1963
Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1932-
Nov. 15, 1962, Jan. 10, 1964
Kennedy, Ethel. 1928-
Nov. 12, 1963
Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.
Oct. 23, 1-959, Dec. 28, 1959, Nov. 16, 1960, Dec. 6, 1960, July 26, 1960, Oct. 10, 1960, Oct. 16, 1960, Mar. 9, 1961, Sept. 11, 1961, Dec. 1, 1961, Feb. 9, 1962, July 9, 1962, Oct. 22, 1962, Feb. 12, 1963, July 3, 1963, Nov. 22, 1963, Aug. 12, 1960
Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.
1960, July 12, 1962, June 3, 1963, July 17, 1963, Nov. 23, 1963
Kerner, Otto, 1908-1976.
Apr. 4, 1962
Kerr, Robert S., 1896-1963.
July 10, 1952
Lacy, Ernest J.
Sept. 24, 1952, 1953, 1956 undated
Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.
Sept. 21, 1952
Lesinski, T. John, 1914-
Apr. 3, 1962, Apr. 2, 1964
Lippmann, Walter, 1889-1974.
June 28, 1965
Long, Russell B.
Mar. 28, 1962
Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.
Nov. 11, 1955
Louchheim, Katie, 1903-
Nov. 23, 1953, 1954, June 2, 1955, Oct. 18, 1955, June 28, 1955, Mar. 30, 1956, Aug. 10, 1956, Aug. 13, 1956, Nov. 6, 1958, 1959-1960, Mar. 20, 1961, Apr. 3, 1962, June 8, 1962, Apr. 30, 1964
McCormack, John W., 1891-
May 3, 1949, Aug. 1, 1956, Aug. 7, 1956, Apr. 11, 1962, Mar. 31, 1964, Dec. 28, 1965, Jan. 1, 1966, Mar. 11, 1966
McGovern, George S. (George Stanley), 1922-
June 23, 1961
McIntyre, Thomas J., 1915-
May 8, 1967
McKeithen, John Julian, 1918-
Apr. 13, 1965
McKellar, Kenneth Douglas, 1869-1957.
Feb. 28, 1950
McKinney, Frank Edward, 1904-1974.
Aug. 21, 1952, July 31, 1956, May 2, 1962
McNamara, Patrick Vincent, 1894-1966.
May 21, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954, July 5, 1955
McNamara, Robert S., 1916-
Mar. 2, 1964
Magnuson, Warren Grant, 1905-
Mar. 1962, Feb. 1, 1965
Mansfield, Mike, 1903-
Jan. 23, 1962, Apr. 11, 1962
Mayo, Leonard W.
1950, 1952, Aug. 17, 1953, Nov. 24, 1953
Mesta, Perle.
Feb. 18, 1954
Mitchell, Stephen Arnold, 1903-
1952-1955, May 2, 1962
Monroney, Mike, 1902-
Nov. 5, 1952
Montoya, Joseph Manuel, 1915-
June 3, 1965
Moody, Blair, 1902-1954.
Feb. 11, 1952, Aug. 6, 1952, Oct. 8, 1952
Morse, Wayne Lyman, 1900-
July 12, 1962
Moyers, Bill D.
Mar. 18, 1964, Apr. 8, 1964, Apr. 25, 1964
Muskie, Edmund S., 1914-
Sept. 20, 1954, Sept. 24, 1954, Oct. 11, 1954
Neuberger, Maurine Brown, 1907-
Sept. 29, 1961, Mar. 9, 1966
O'Brien, Lawrence Francis.
Jan. 29, 1964, Apr. 8, 1964, Sept. 29, 1964
Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1929-
Dec. 1, 1961, Jan. 8, 1961
Peabody, Endicott, 1920-
Jan. 17, 1962
Peck, Gregory, 1916-
Oct. 16, 1965
Powell, Adam Clayton, 1908-1972.
Mar. 28, 1962
Proxmire, William.
Dec. 28, 1964
Quimby, Thomas H. E. (Thomas Howard Emerson), 1918-
May 31, 1955, 1959-1960
Rayburn, Sam, 1882-1961.
May 3, 1949
Reuther, Roy L., 1968.
Oct. 23, 1952, July 6, 1956, July 16, 1956, Feb. 1, 1965
Reuther, Victor G. (Victor George), 1912-
Aug. 22, 1950
Reuther, Walter, 1907-1970.
Jan. 23, 1953
Ribicoff, Abraham, 1910-
Jan. 30, 1961, Jan. 18, 1963
Roberts, Dennis Joseph, 1903-
Jan. 30, 1956
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman.
Jan. 27, 1966
Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.
Mar. 19, 1962, Oct. 10, 1953
Roosevelt, Elliot, 1910-
Dec. 11, 1964
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1914-1988.
June 1, 1952, Apr. 7, 1964, June 16, 1965
Roosevelt, James, 1907-
Apr. 4, 1962
Rusk, Dean, 1909-
Sept. 8, 1961, May 1, 1963, Feb. 20, 1967
Salinger, Pierre.
July 8, 1960, Apr. 16, 1961, Apr. 20, 1961, May 4, 1962, June 8, 1962
Sallade, George Wahr, 1922-
Aug. 30, 1965
Sanford, Terry, 1917-
Apr. 2, 1962
Scholle, August, 1904-
May 19, 1954, Dec. 22, 1960
Smathers, George Armistead, 1913-
June 22, 1956
Sorenson, Theodore C.
Aug. 29, 1966
Sparkman, John, 1899-1985.
Oct. 7, 1952, Mar. 28, 1962, June 7, 1967, Nov. 22, 1967
Staebler, Burnette.
Mar. 13, 1959
Staebler, Neil, 1905-
1948-1950, Feb. 27, 1951, Apr. 11, 1951, 1952-1957, Jan. 14, 1958, Feb. 25, 1958, Mar. 14, 1958, Sept. 1, 1959, June 6, 1960, Aug. 22, 1960, 1961, Jan. 8, 1962, Feb. 19, 1962, Dec. 10, 1962, May 26, 1964, Oct. 31, 1964, 1965-1966
Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965.
Oct. 7, 1952, Nov. 17, 1952, Nov. 25, 1952, Jan. 7, 1953, 1956, Apr. 6, 1959, Apr. 28, 1959, Mar. 1960, Sept. 23, 1960
Swainson, John Burley, 1925-
Feb. 11, 1961, Nov. 14, 1961, Apr. 17, 1962
Symington, Stuart, 1901-
Oct. 26, 1959, Mar. 31, 1962, Sept. 26, 1967
Talmadge, Herman E. (Herman Eugene), 1913-
July 21, 1950, July 28, 1950, Oct. 7, 1950, Mar. 29, 1962
Todd, Paul Harold, 1921-
Mar. 11, 1965
Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.
Apr. 3, 1948, Aug. 15, 1949, May 16, 1955, Jan. 4, 1960, Apr. 2, 1964
Tydings, Joseph Davies, 1928-
Mar. 26, 1965
Tyroler, Charles.
Nov. 25, 1957, Dec. 19, 1957, 1958, Jan. 22, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Feb. 25, 1960
Udall, Stewart L.
Mar. 5, 1964
Vivian, Weston Edward, 1924-
Mar. 1965, Sept. 3, 1965
Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand) 1910-
Apr. 24, 1959
Weaver, Robert Clifton, 1907-
Apr. 1, 1964
Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-
May 29, 1948, Oct. 23, 1948, 1949-1950, Jan. 2, 1951, Apr. 26, 1951, Nov. 22, 1951, 1952-1957, Jan. 25, 1951, Aug. 27, 1958, Oct. 30, 1958, 1959-1960
Williams, G. Mennen, Mrs.
Jan. 21, 1951, June 7, 1956, 1959
Williams, Harrison A., 1919-
Jan. 22, 1963
Wirtz, Willard, 1912-
Feb. 28, 1964, Mar. 6, 1964
Yarborough, Ralph Webster, 1903-
Jan. 31, 1962
Youngdahl, Luther W., 1896-
Mar. 6, 1950